<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="lagna_year">
        <item>
            Ability to build economic strength and see progress in partnerships. Rahu 2nd is a powerful movement that can bring good results in terms of wealth. Makes sudden capital gains. Deposits have the potential to increase wealth.

Those who are unlucky in the Rahu birth center should be a little more careful. Unexpected troubles can also lead to property damage due to their agitation.

Time is better for education. Exams can be won. Progress can be seen in higher education.

Care should be taken in domestic life. Friendships can happen. Make only promises that can be fulfilled. Be careful about the use of words.
Take care of body health. Sudden bruising can also cause feverish knee-related distress.

If the birth horoscope is the 3rd moon, then The eighth luner Erashtaka period so So engage in regular religious activities.
        </item>

        <item>Ability to resume abandoned work and complete well. Jobs are cheap. Increases economic strength. It is possible to get the attraction of the opposite sex very well.

Jobs disrupted after April 6. Job-related troubles are caused by their negligence. Education can be successful. Higher education can be successful. Interferes with marriage proposals. Foreign employment creates profits. Family unity can be disrupted.

Those who are weakly located in the birth center of Venus, Rahu can fall prey to deception. Punishment causes accidents. Urgency can disrupt their activities.

Headaches, urinary incontinence may occur. Since the 2nd lunar month of the birth horoscope is the eighth lunar Erashtaka time, engage in regular religious activities.
</item>
        <item>Gemini

Sagittarius Saturn 8 Rahu 12 Guru 7 is a passing year so it is a year where one cannot expect as many good results as expected. It is a year of job disruption and unexpected wealth loss, stress, property issues, legal issues, insults, and so on. There are many barriers to marriage.

Education runs successfully from March 11 to March 30, July 07 to July 25, August 26 to November 21. There is a possibility of winning the exam. But troublesome obstacles to education cause boredom.

Kidney disease, intestinal diseases, foot, and eye diseases can occur. Must be vegetarian.

If the planets Rahu and Saturn are auspicious, these conditions are auspicious.

For those who are in the Moon sign in the birth horoscope, unfortunate effects increase due to the simultaneous operation of two Erashtaka. It is very important to engage in regular religious activities.
</item>
        <item>
The income level will improve during the period when Jupiter travels from April 6th to 7th. Those obstacles that have existed so far will be removed. From then on, there will be some obstacles in the future. If guru good brings good results. Rahu 11 is on the move so exam wins educational facilities are available. Sudden wealth gain positions, powers, good social status, recognition, publicity. Dating is successful. Have children.

From March 17th to April 10th, from May 4th to May 29th, from September 6th to October 2nd, real estate gains, positive gains. Disrupts higher education after September 16th.

Rahu 3, 11 are highly beneficial at birth. If the Moon is 12th, the lunar eighth Erashtaka period increases unfortunate time. Bodhi Pooja, Pirith recitation, and Seth poem should be done.
</item>
        <item>At the beginning of the year, economic strength was not so good and gradually improved after April 16. The passing of the 6th planet of the Guru raises some obstacles in that regard.

Rahu 10th is on the move so it interferes with employment. Raises questions of superiors. Have good relationships with superiors. Job transfers may occur. There is a time to be mindful throughout the coming year. Various losses can be incurred due to his own negligence.

Causes property problems. You have to be very responsible in dealing with relatives. Causes chest related diseases. Increases skin disease conditions.

Control oily foods. Will cause abdominal distress. If the Moon is in the 11th house of the birth horoscope, then the lunar eighth Erashtaka will increase the incidence of diseases etc. Engage in regular religious activities.
</item>
        <item>With the passing of Guru Shani, Mercury 5th at the beginning of the year, there will be progress in education. There will also be progress in higher education in May. Wedding proposals are successful. Good for joint ventures.

Moving to the 9th planet Rahu will increase the odds.

Job interruptions cause trouble. Can damage their condition. Social status is disrupted. Destroys recognition. Makes room to stay away from religious activities. The elders have some misunderstandings with the clergy. This situation must be understood and acted upon. Makes children sick. But educational conditions can be successful.

If Rahu is powerful at birth he makes foreign trips. Property benefits. Receive higher education.

If the Moon is 10th at birth, the lunar eighth Erashtaka period is created

If Rahu, Mars, Saturn directions, be more careful. Religious practices can eliminate unhappiness.

</item>
        <item>Ability to collaborate with others and look at issues sympathetically.

At the beginning of the year, Mars becomes powerful, resulting in positive gains. The period from April 06 to September 14 is when the teacher and Mercury become powerful and the children’s education is successful and there are also sudden capital gains. Higher education opportunities. Exams are won.

Expectations are fulfilled as the 4th Saturn of Yoga becomes powerful. Supported by older relatives. It solves property problems and also causes mental distress.

Rahu 8th and Ketu 2nd are moving and auspicious situations arise. Makes sudden capital gains. But adversely affects health. Causes diseases of the throat, stomach, and feet. A legal issue can be resolved.

If the Moon is 9th in the Birth horoscope, the lunar eighth Erashtaka period will also increase the bad situation. If Saturn, Guru, and Rahu are powerful, evil will be reduced. Engage in regular religious activities.
</item>
        <item>It is a year in which we have the ability to overcome many obstacles and succeed.

Good for parents. Makes vehicle profits. Enemy persecution is avoided. Good for kids with basic education. Property issues are avoided. Homes are available for repair.

You will be able to take the lead. Increases the popularity of those involved in social service politics. He gets a good place. Gets public acclaim. Profits from foreign affairs. Even opponents help.

If guru and Rahu unfortunate, These results are not given.

Problems arise in married life. Joint ventures fail. Dealing with relatives also creates disadvantages as well as divisions. Their health is deteriorating.

If the Moon is 8th in the birth horoscope,  It is also the Moon luner eighth Erashtaka.

Such people must do Bodhi Pooja, recite Seth poems, and offer medicines. Worship the Triple Gem daily and say Moor Pirith, Kanda Pirith, Chanda Pirith, and Suriya Pirith.
</item>
        <item>Saturn is an erashtaka error state. Sagittarians may face some setbacks due to late payments, but the arrival of a second teacher creates a positive profit.

Deposits can increase wealth. Creates job advancement. Able to cultivate their spiritual qualities.

After April 6, 2021, good times will dawn for the brothers. He also has positive thoughts. Innate abilities develop. The effort pays off. Rahu is the 6th planet to travel throughout the year, which can lead to good social prestige.

Creates new revenue streams. Enemy troubles are suppressed. It is possible to achieve political victories. As the cones also move in the 12th, eye weakness can occur. If the cones are intermediate, the health condition will deteriorate.

Marriage proposals are confirmed during the period from July 07 to July 25 and from August 26 to November 02 when the 7th lord Mercury is in power.

Job promotions are also available. This time the partnership will be successful. If it is the 7th moon in the birth center, it increases the bad situation.
</item>
        <item>Sagittarius Saturn moves in the zodiac throughout the year so that even if there is some delay in the work, it is possible to create new avenues of wealth. Able to lead locally or not. Respected by others.

The movement of the 5th planet Rahu may interfere with the educational activities of the children. If Rahu is powerful in the birth center, it is also possible to do well in education.

In addition to educational activities, he also engages in other external activities. This in turn disrupts basic education.

March 17 - April 10, May 04 to 29 and September 06 to October 02. It is better to apply for new jobs.

Gets to do well in home life. Social deposits are obtained to create wealth.

Horoscopes on the 6th of the Moon at birth are subject to the eighth cycle of the cycle, which causes deterioration in health and mental distress.

Daily worship of the Triple Gem, Chanda Piritha and Suriya Piritha. Being vegetarian is great.
</item>
        <item>Sagittarius Saturn and guru as long as the 12th is moving, Rahu is the 4th cone and the 10th cone is accessible.

According to is accessible. The year goes by giving mixed results. Outside the village is a year that makes the most of your progress.

 And with Saturn 12th approaching, progress in the first half of the year will be slower and costs will be higher.

There are also legal issues to be faced. It is a time of economic decline.

Rahu 4th and Ketu 10th move powerfully so that they are able to do it with satisfaction even if there are some obstacles in their career.

After April 06, you will be able to do your homework well. It interferes with the activities of the children who are being educated. But with effort, you can win the exam. A change of residence may occur. Focusing on the affairs of others rather than one\'s own will interfere with one\'s own work.

Saturn has a bad Erashtaka situation, so pay attention to your health. Engage in regular religious activities. Praise God for Mora Piritha, Chanda Piritha and Suriya Piritha.

</item>
        <item>The year begins with the Sagittarius Guru moving to the 8th place.

Mars will also be in second place until February 22nd, which will increase deposit wealth. Income level rises.

During the period from April 06 to September 14 to November 20, there will be an increase in employment. New jobs make profits. Education is successful. Passing exams makes student profits.

Rahu 3rd and Cone 9th are moving so it brings a lot of good results. Increases business profits. There are unexpected profits. Is praised among others.

Homelife goes well. Positions bring profits according to knowledgeability. Able to show innate abilities. Tends to be religious. Good luck going abroad.

Saturn 11th travel causes foot-related distress. Causes skin diseases.

Involve yourself in religious activities as much as possible to overcome such persecution. Offer Pirikara for Dharma Dhana. If the 4th moon is in the birth horoscope, then the lunar eighth erashtaka period also passes.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lagna_names">
        <item>Aries</item>
        <item>Taurus</item>
        <item>Gemini</item>
        <item>Cancer</item>
        <item>Leo</item>
        <item>Virgo</item>
        <item>Libra</item>
        <item>Scorpio</item>
        <item>Sagittarius</item>
        <item>Capricorn</item>
        <item>Aquarius</item>
        <item>Pisces</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="kendare_day">
        <item>Your eyes are attracted to others. Most people will tell you as soon as they see you. "Oh, your eyes are so beautiful" "His eyes are so weird" You have such a special pair of eyes. I like to wear mostly white clothes. Their hair is very thin. These people have the ability to speak in a way that attracts the attention of others and never wants to hurt or hurt anyone. Although very intelligent, these people are always tempted to fall in love with men and women who are older than they are. Also, these people are very susceptible to leprosy.</item>
        <item>You are the inheritor of a very cruel-looking eye magazine. The look of these people is very unusual. The body of these people who are red in the eyes is not so tall. By nature, the body is a bit fat. Still, the thinking of these young men is very bad. At any rate, these people, who are angry at the slightest thing, are going to be very strong in the militancy they are born with.</item>
        <item>These are people who live a very simple normal life with a very light heart. These people, who always speak kind words, are known for their modesty and ability to attract the attention of others. These people who love literature and the art of writing also excel at them. These people are very interested in learning about different sciences especially things like occult sciences. It is very easy for others to be deceived by the gossip of those born on Wednesdays who are always deceitful.</item>
        <item>These people are born with radiant skin. Even though it is black, the preferred way to see your skin is bright. These hairy, copper-colored men are very wise. These people, who are very intelligent and far-sighted about everything, lead a very pious life. People born on Thursdays who have very calm traits have a mucous body that suffers from skin diseases.</item>
        <item>Bright eyeglasses are a valuable gift that these people are born with. Because of the brilliance of these eyes, these people are constantly attracted to others. If you are a girl who was born on a Friday, you are very lucky. Because you can claim long hair. Even if you are a man, your hair will grow back quickly. These guys, who are always very fond of witchcraft, have a very wide round face. They are also more likely to enjoy sex and to stand out.</item>
        <item>These people also have long hair. These people, who have slender limbs and long teeth, have wide teeth and do not care much about anything. As a result, a lot of suffering happens to these people. But these people are very good at imitating others.</item>
        <item>These guys have a square face. The look in his eyes is not that funny either. But these people with courageous traits do not fall in front of anything. As well as that unwavering strength, these people have firm ideas and firm policies. They have a medium-sized body and are very virtuous, intelligent, but at times their minds are filled with evil thoughts as well as cruelty.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="kendare_month">
        <item>If you were born in January, you\'re the one who can thrive by focusing on an active, agile business. These are kept in mind without revealing secrets. If married at a young age, there are good wives and mothers. People born this month love to have fun and play games.
And if money promises to do something very carefully, they have the good fortune to do so. These people are very happy when their ideas are fulfilled. Sometimes they feel sad for no reason. The gemstone to be worn is a "ruby".</item>
        <item>If you were born in the month of February, you will have the power to bring about economic growth as well as economic decline. They are full of many things but do not care about time. A woman born this month can be bad at a young age but after growing up she will have good wives, loving caregivers and good mothers. Both men and women born this month will be happier after marriage. The gemstone to be worn is the "pollen".</item>
        <item>If you were born in March, your limbs are strong. For that reason, there are skilled workers or playwrights. Very fond of beautiful things. Rarely strives for his own improvement. Commitment to the well-being of others. Both men and women born in March are not greedy for money. They are proactive and optimistic about the future. Appropriate gemstones are red beads.</item>
        <item>If you were born in April, you are intelligent. In some cases, they even have the privilege of being promoted to a higher position. Confidence in others is very low and there is a tendency to be jealous of the happiness of others. Nor does he want to forgive a mistake. Fancy to wear fancy jewellery - will be interested in dressing up. When it comes to spending money, it can be a daunting task. They will decide to give up regardless of the marriage contract. They will build marital relationships on their own. Suitable gemstone diamond.</item>
        <item>If you were born in May you will be encouraged. Are kind. Enjoy playing games.
They live happily ever after. The desire to play interferes with their work. They are very edgy. Very good for those born this month
Has a bearing capacity. They are very annoyed that others do not remember certain things. They do as they please.
Will also be involved in giving advice on the work of others. Both men and women born this month will be immediately irritable.
The most suitable gemstone to wear is emerald or tattoo gem.</item>
        <item>If you were born in June you are rarely happy. You do not know what you want. They want to have it all, no matter where they are.
He cannot tolerate others living well. They will decide today to do the work they regret tomorrow without any hesitation. These are torture
Compassionate aid will also help those who are suffering from pain. Impressions are gained in a fluid, global, diffused way. Will also like the error view of others. They are naturally jealous and do not trust others
There is also a tendency. Their irritability is manifested by the provision of nails. Gem-white would be the official fit.
</item>
        <item>People born in the month are usually known for their wisdom. They are virtuous and noble. Pleasure for features and travel
Will show. That quality will only get worse with age. The Vanitha Party, born in July, is soft-spoken. Spread their good qualities
They also need light and encouragement to go. The male party born in July will often prefer to be at home. For those born this month
The gem to wear is emerald.
</item>
        <item>If you were born in August: will be able to command. Their love or passion is very powerful. Those born this month do a great job
Are adept at. Will act at its own discretion. There is also a tendency to help the suffering of others. Youthful. Born in August
It is said that people get married twice. Ideas about the job field or the business sector are very good. They are also good at reasoning. Second to others
There are those who have non-opinions. You can trust money transactions and secrets. The most suitable gemstone to wear is the red gem.
</item>
        <item>If you were born in September, people born in this month are kind. No fuss. Secrets can be trusted. Are quite greedy. Do not break words
They also have great qualities. Prefers new clothes. Part of their lives are spent walking for two or three years. Everyone
Will show intimacy with. People born this month will be in good health. But alcohol can lead to many diseases
Opportunity is created. Pearls would also be appropriate for those born this month.
</item>
        <item>What if you were born in October? Will be pious. They do not care much about money. Will use their money unnecessarily.
Spends in vain. Have the energy to be superior people. But small things can make you feel discouraged and discouraged. Little things will be forgotten.
They forget their promises about certain things. Can\'t trust deals. Women born this month will be more passionate about men and men will be more passionate about women. For those born this month, it may be appropriate to wear a crowbar.
</item>
        <item>If you were born in November, you are a very thoughtful person with screen ideas. Will act at its discretion. Will also be rhetorical.
Will also earn the respect of others. It will also help them to do as they please and achieve victory. Spending childhood playing games
Because of this you will have to repent later in life. You get leverage to grow your business faster. Their association will also improve.
Pearls are suitable as a suitable gemstone.
</item>
        <item>What if you were born in December? Those born this month are diligent. There are those who grow fast and those who fall. Always say the word of truth
Are charged. Money transactions can be trusted. They are law-abiding people who act according to their heart. Making quick friendships with others
There is also a talent. There is devotion to religion. Will also be interested in helping the needy. Their weakness is that no matter how advanced they are,
To promote the progress of others. The ruby to wear goes to the pollen gem.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="kendare_zodiac_img">
        <item>The middle is the most beautiful body. Nice elongated neck and clusters of hair and beard and eyebrows. The good horn is the soil. Bends slightly when moving. Diligent. Too many sticks.</item>
        <item>It has a broad forehead and a slightly larger body than the median. The neck is fat.
Is coarse hair. The common cold is high.</item>
        <item>Tall is a fully grown body. The outstretched arm is the foot. The features are the remains. Often taller than the perpa mana. Moves to the tune. Be clear words.</item>
        <item>Is a medium sized slender body. Are elongated organs. Pleasant face. Is a mild appearance. Someone with a pale body or delicate skin. Coarse stuff can\'t be used.</item>
        <item>It is a fully grown body with broad shoulders. Stomach is thin. Looks radiant. Is a big head. Is red skin. The shoulders are sometimes too wide.</item>
        <item>Is a delicate body. The midpoint is approx. Sometimes even smaller than the median size. There is a squeaking sound. Is moving diligently. Looks younger than age.</item>
        <item>It is a tall, medium-sized body. There will be a pleasing appearance. There are sharp eyes. After middle age, the back of the head forms a plate.</item>
        <item>Are well-developed organs. Is healthy. Is curly hair.</item>
        <item>Fully grown features are the image. Is a broad forehead. Sometimes the pare ct is higher than the dimension. Is the raised elongated nose. The gold is Isakes. Is red skin. The feature is the complete image.</item>
        <item>Thin is a weak body. Thin face and big teeth.</item>
        <item>The median is a body of features. The environment is facing. Are colorful hair. Looks kind.</item>
        <item>It is a short obese body with small limbs. The shoulders are narrow. The hip area is wide. Are shining eyes. Sometimes the eyes are bigger than the parasite. Often red eyes. Isakes like shiny soft silk. After middle age, the body beats. The meat is loose.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="kendare_zodiac_attr">
        <item>Since Mars had a lot of warlike zeal, those born in Aries have a glorious sense of progress with high ideas. Someone who wants what they want at the right time. Gets it anyway. He is not happy to sacrifice his personal desires for the sake of others. He wants whatever he wants.
The desire for fame, the desire to be at the forefront, and the desire to move forward lead to victory and re-emergence. Champion of Action. Also diligent. A man does not want to be submissive to anyone other than his wife or a woman to his husband. The spouse becomes very devoted to the spouse. Someone who cares about the winning intuition. Hunger is unbearable. Often needs a little bit of food. Always proud. Those born in Aries are no more fit for debate. During the debate, he raises a quarrel that he could not win and hopes to win. But there is an insight that is immediately understood.
Do not hesitate to fight. There is no fear. Do not like small things. Suitable for big business. Are high thoughts. Suddenly things change. But if you decide to go it cheap and risk the low bandwidth you are only fooling yourself. The greatest heroes in the world are born in Aries. Zodiac. This is the most powerful sign because it starts with Aries.
Capricorn and Cancer are justified because it is in the middle of two. But not so much in Libra. Weaknesses include impatience and a lack of respect for peace. Do not like to do small things.
</item>
        <item>People born in the Taurus of Venus love artifacts. Thinks to live easily. There is a mind that does not bend as if to prove the quality of the screen. Able to keep in mind. Anger is also slow. If so, getting better is slow. There are mysteries that others cannot understand. He keeps even the smallest things in mind and presents and speaks when needed.

Able to fight until a permanent victory. He is very careful about money and his worldly things. Don\'t be afraid to spend money on clothes like Venus. Mind the land. Feels like growing flowers. A little reluctant to spend on others. Is quite greedy. Absolute waste in money transactions.
No diligence. But is able to continue working. He is not one who kneels before his opponent. Is prone to natural phenomena. Rural life with flowers, fruits and trees is better than urban life. Very good for the story. Speaks with facts. He holds on to his ideas. Not happy to act according to the knowledge of others. He thinks he knows someone. Thoughts weigh on the worldly side. Weaknesses seem to be a bit greedy and a desire to overcome too many desires for comfort. That is why enemies arise. The lawsuit was probably settled out of court.
</item>
        <item>Those born in Gemini, the male constellation, have a better understanding of human life. There is also a sense of humanity and compassion. He has the wisdom to do what he wants at the right time. In the story, he speaks to show above as if he knew everything. Not a brilliant thinker. Opinions change frequently. Because of this, things that start do not end as expected. Are contradictory. If the Buddha is in a powerful and good position, he is likely to be a brilliant orator, poet, or composer. Often engaged in two or more professions. While doing one, think of another.
Sometimes Because of the women, Wealth is damaged. If there is no sin in the ninth, then there is good religious devotion. The walk is refreshing. As long as he is engaged in the work, he acts as a master of that work. Someone who is friendly. Undoubtedly engages in strange work with no previous experience. Weaknesses seem to be the unfinished work that begins, the abandonment, the change of mind from day to day, and the lack of calmness.
</item>
        <item>Cancer is the highest point in Uttarayana. Those who are born in the sign of Cancer, the lord of the mind, are astute thinkers with high thoughts. Able to do what is seen. Because of his good nature, he trusts other people\'s buses and bends to them. Kariya is the champion. Are noble ideas. Seems like a straight thinker. There are very few hidden secrets. Is rich. Probably the super rich. The love of wife and children makes the house comfortable. They are brave as well as cowardly. Allies make as well as lose. A distant fear of disaster. That is, it is more straightforward.
Excessive shock at the calamity of others. He is fond of small animals, small children, those who are inferior to him, and the weaker party, or women. All suffering trials become paradoxical even in the midst of humiliation. Patience is low. Anger does not last. Thinks about big business. The same is true of affairs. Suitable for leading large businesses.
Wealth and status rise. The Moon is in the sign of the zodiac for the most part. Used for religious ceremonies. They are very good at giving advice. He warns of the safety of others, but he does not take them seriously. Gets an incomparable wife. The great men of the world were born in this sign. Even now. Being at the peak of Iru\'s ascending journey means supernatural ideas. Weaknesses appear to be over-sympathy, irritability, impatience, and elevation.
</item>
        <item>Ravi Thera was born in Sinha as a brave man with a strong desire for self-improvement. Courage is the key to survival. Self-confidence is the key to undertaking any serious endeavour. Small work and small workers are disgusted by high expectations. Wherever he goes, he dominates.

The mind that does not change until the last moment comes to the fore and the paradigm shift. He specializes in magic, poetry, and painting. They are also good at it. A person who acts with mindfulness. That is the victory of life. One does not offend oneself in the first place. Is proud.
</item>
        <item>Those born in the sign of Virgo, the apex of Mercury, the lord of wisdom, are born with a clever wisdom in resolving. Many are sympathetic. Blames others. It is very fragrant. Someone with low self-confidence. The commotion is such that he writes two letters, finishes them all, and reopens them to see if the real letter is in the right envelope. Explains even the smallest detail when saying something. Says again and again. It is customary to do more housework. Even the furniture is thought to be in good condition.
Documents are kept neat and tidy. Spends time on even the smallest things you don’t need. Misses big things. Would like to give. It is also palatable to taste. Friendships do not last. Is healthy. And there is a lot of fear of disease. Eats medicine for missing ailments. The earth is mindful. Is prone to grow. Spending money is very frugal. Someone who works harder than you think. If Rahu is in Virgo, most of these qualities are like this. If the Buddha is powerful, fast words or laughter or jokes are too much. Weaknesses are seen as a lack of self-confidence, distrust of others, interference in small things, and guilt.
</item>
        <item>Someone with a kind heart with direct compassion. Respects justice, support and kindness. Loves peace. Wisdom, ingenuity, and eloquence are inherited. One who has the wisdom to see something before. Anger subsides very quickly. Desires craftsmanship.
Is proficient in business. Takes the lead in administering justice. Justice is balanced on a scale. Unlike Aries, Libra likes to suffer by sacrificing his personal comforts for the sake of others. Respects altruism more than selfishness. Are high thoughts. Perfect for a natural show is addictive.
Respects peace in debate. The mild sweetness often results in a sacrificial nature. Is mindful of society. Feels like walking. Seems primarily in public service. Able to win the goodwill of others. Humanity is highly respected. Since the dragon is between the two dragons, it is in the middle of the two worldly supernatural qualities. Weaknesses seem to be the desire for artifacts and the desire for frequent refinement.
</item>
        <item>Be a quick one. Be brave. No secrets. There is a tendency to kick the block and move on. He has a fertile heart. It is also wise. A very diligent person. Do not lose courage. That is, one who immediately regains lost courage. There is a high degree of pride. Likes and dislikes criticism.
There are faults in the opinions of others. Go talk about them and make them unhappy in vain. Next to Aries, Scorpio is good at action. Many things can be done as seen. No desire to stockpile. There is wisdom that is immediately understood. Eager to search. Paddy has long been regarded as one of the most revered customs in the world, but it can be broken down into a series of rituals. There is a tendency for a carpenter to look after only his own affairs. Those born in the sign of Scorpio have a prominent position. There is no such thing as accepting something from above.
 Accepted after a good understanding. Because of his self-confidence in his abilities, he postpones things until the last moment. I will do it whenever I want. Weaknesses seem to be the ability to let others know their ideas without limits, temper tantrums, the desire to play games, and a bit of jealousy.
</item>
        <item>Those born in Guru Sagittarius are gifted. Works straightforward. There are broad ideas. The same goes for action. Hopes of rising to prominence. Justice is like life. Injustice to another or another cannot be tolerated.
If so, it\'s because of someone else. Just as the Gemini zodiac sign misses the work it started, the opposite Sagittarius zodiac sign does nothing but finish what it started. The same thing applies to urgency. Philosophical theorists desire to learn higher teachings. Because the ninth in the zodiac ring belongs to them.

Is his inexhaustible wealth. Good luck and good luck. Words are as wise as commandments. The action is encouraging as well as dangerous. Diligence and efficiency work well and the business thrives. Modesty Program Functionality is the stepping stone to one\'s progress. Sounds like something that has been prepared for a long time.
Horses love such games around horseshoes. But often the humble modest life pays off. There is a tendency to transact carefully. Weaknesses appear to be unwarranted distrust, inconsistent encounters with dangerous things, sudden change of opinion, and accidents. It is not good for Sagittarius to have eight moons. Self-inflicted warts but disease-causing. Being on Saturn 5 is a position that gives many virtues.
Then he comes forward to fight for justice as if he had no sympathy. Just as Sagittarius is made up of two bodies, people born in Sagittarius have two qualities. Once upon a time, without any respect, he jumped forward to do whatever he wanted and worked at a cost.
Once upon a time there was a lot of patience, mindfulness and frugality that would not interfere with such a thing. Anything new is not new to Sagittarius. It takes courage to do what is right. It does not do what is illegal because of justice. The Sagittarius does not sue on his own accord. Try to avoid it whenever possible.
</item>
        <item>Since Saturn is the lord of Pathavi, the person born in Capricorn has a desire to gain power. Someone with less subtle thoughts and more caries. Selfishness, which works for its own benefit, prevails. Thinks long and hard for that. There is no confidence that the profit will be received until it is in hand. The relentlessness of suffering leads to victory. A person born in Capricorn does not spend his time lazily and idle. Worldly desires are very powerful. Wisdom or budgeting on the subject of economics is paramount.
The greed for money and the desire for power seem to be somewhat miserly. Thinks big of the little things of others. They talk big. Large businesses have the control to take the lead. Even in times of disaster, there is a reluctance to ask for help. All work has to go through a gloomy melancholy period. Winning is like going forward to win as well as wanting to be invisible when losing. Not as expressive as the narrator.
Friends are declining. Wealth is accumulated just by thinking of investing in some profit margin in everything we do. Suitable for heavy work and front work. Suitable for political activities. Those born in Capricorn, the opposite of Pisces, love the earth. No higher thoughts. Everything must be worldly and mundane. This is where Iru\'s Dakshinayana ends. Weaknesses seem to be overwork and greed.
</item>
        <item>One who respects the natural state. A human being. A passion for learning deep things. Women know the boundaries. Knows the science of warfare. Is adept at learning the art of telling the characters of others. The association of good friends
 Does. They are capable of recognizing who their true friends are. Finds out what to do. Or wait until someone else does and learns. His qualities are perseverance, patience, and harmony of heart. Sticks to subtle actions. Be wise but be reluctant to accept new things. Because he has the capacity to bear, he does not forget what he once did. Suitable for chemical testing. The world is for ordinary people, not for the lucky few. Is an opinion holder.

In national work, it works for the benefit of the general public and the underprivileged. One who has good qualities on the inside rather than on the outside. The mind has the courage to use the body to the fullest. Often those born in Aquarius win in the end. He is a person who has a strong love for his people. Often the ascetic eventually thinks of coming to life or such a state.
Or we may be trying to make excuses for not doing something that we should have done. In philosophical theories, deeper scholars are interested. They are good at learning. He learns to teach them for the good of others rather than to put them into action. This was Saturn\'s zodiac sign, but he does not aspire to self-gain, like Capricorn. That is why there are great men who have won real public persecution. Orphanages, prisons, health halls to help. Bail helps them to suffer. Or does their job. Weaknesses seem to be caused by the desire to live alone, to face dark times when there are no activities, and the lack of focus on worldly things that can sometimes lead to laziness.
</item>
        <item>Is diligent in infancy. Is showy. Be a straight man with a melting heart. Bends as a mark of respect for the opinions of others. There is a tendency to turn to weird ideas and new things. Likes to spend time enjoying delicious food. Worldly progress is slow. Respects the supernatural. Able to engage in two or more activities. Is very kind. When giving something to a poor person, he never asks you what happened and whether you can do a job.

Is kind. When giving something to a poor person, he never asks you what happened and whether you can do a job. It also does not ask a patient what the disease is or how it was developed. Forgiveness is the ultimate essence of Pisces. Does not betray even the enemy.

Wealth in the world seldom thrives because of a passion for public service, a lack of respect for gifted crops, and a lack of selfishness. He may also be poor because of the high level of self-sacrifice and generosity. Trust in Pisces will never be broken. No matter how kind the animal is, it cannot tolerate suffering. Often works to help them.
A growing tree is reluctant to break even a vine. Pisces does not make his good qualities known to the country. He enjoys them for the sake of his own mind. Weaknesses include excessive affection, self-destructive compassion, and generosity in trusting in the promises of others. These are the virtues of the superior.
</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="kendare_zodiac_dis">
        <item>Inflammatory bowel disease, brain disease, abdominal pain, sudden fainting, insomnia, sudden loss of consciousness, mild illness. Suitable for those born in Aries are the mango teal, diamond, and white blue.</item>
    <item>All skin diseases are easily formed. Diseases of the head, neck and chest, sore throat, phlegm, asthma, sepsis are easily formed. Over time, constipation, high blood pressure or sepsis, and dehydration can lead to blood clots and loss of life. It is good for those born in Taurus to wear tattoos.</item>
    <item>Lung diseases, such as pneumonia, pneumonia, asthma, bronchitis, and bronchitis are also common. For those born with a twin, it is best to wear an aquamarine or light blue stone.</item>
    <item>Gastric or peptic ulcer: It is the most common type of gastric ulcer. For those born with cancer, it is best to wear a tattoo or water tattoo.</item>
    <item>-</item>
    <item>It can lead to stomach ailments and generally debilitating diseases. For those born in Virgo, it is better to wear light red or light colored stones, Padma Raga.</item>
    <item>Kidney disease can lead to appendicitis, rheumatoid arthritis, and urinary tract infections. For those born in Libra, it is better to wear berries, diamonds and white.</item>
    <item>Diseases of the bladder and uterus include gallstones and acute urinary tract infections. For those born in Scorpio, it is better to wear yellow pollen stones.</item>
    <item>Diseases of the thighs and surrounding paralysis include hemorrhage, dysfunction of the esophagus, hemorrhoids, anal fissures, or swelling of the legs, or block blood vessels in the legs. For those born in Sagittarius, the green-blue mixed name stone or patchwork is good.</item>
    <item>Skin diseases and rheumatic diseases (diseases of the knee joints *, anemia, gout, joint pains, rheumatism, hemorrhoids are easily formed.</item>
    <item>-</item>
    <item>Diseases of the legs from the ankles down, anaemia, edema, anaemia, heart disease, eruptions, etc. Anaemia and swelling of the legs are common with age. For those born of Pisces, it is better to wear pasingala or crystal stones.

We should always equate the two qualities and say only the qualities of the party. It is very difficult to say for sure as there are several asteroids in the zodiac and the nature of the images that the zodiac and they understand are different in many ways. If the teacher is in the sign, he will get fat. But the power of the teacher comes only after the age of forty. The characteristics of the zodiac in which the moon was also often seen.
If the moon is four, then the characteristics of that zodiac sign are very obvious. Being in the tenth house of Mars, the qualities of Mars are manifested in many actions. Therefore, determination should be made with all these things in mind.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="kendare_num">
        <item>No problems in the outside world\n
No. 1 belongs to the power of the planet Ravi. Leadership is always an expectation of courage. You do not offend anyone, nor do you hesitate to punish those who offend you. You will be able to do it right anyway by accepting even the difficult tasks without hesitation. As a prominent figure in society and generation, you have the ability to say what you do not know. You are a person who follows any strategy to win life. But he is not a man of cunning and hypocrisy. You only associate with selected people. So you don’t have unnecessary problems from the outside world.
</item>
        <item>Must be frugal\n
According to your birthday collection, the fate of 2 belongs to the moon. A kind-hearted person who is kind, always restless, saddened by fear and disbelief, and difficult to understand. You are sensitive by birth. Is very fond of art. It is harmful to say what is on the mind without foresight. You are shocked at the calamity of others and you get a lot of trouble because of compassion. Ignorance is your weakness. Keeping the door neat and clean is one of your virtues. Increase your inclination towards social welfare and religious activities. Beware of diseases such as skin aches and pains. Your finances change from time to time. We have to have thrift. You see the shortcomings of others well. But saying that can hurt yourself.
</item>
        <item>Liability is treated as liability\n
The planet that affects your destiny number is Jupiter. You are a very virtuous, fair, kind person. Greed and selfishness can exist. But at a later age it will turn into generosity and compassion. Your youth is full of so much beauty. Later in life he would turn to religion and engage in many meritorious deeds. Slow growth can lead to economic stability. Lack of organization in spending money is one of your shortcomings. You do not go to the extreme of anything. He does not submit to anyone, nor does he submit to others. Someone who can delegate anything responsibly. The thighs may be hard, the air hard. You have creativity, real talent.
</item>
        <item>A law abiding person\n
Rahu and Uranus are the destiny numbers that hold the power of the planets. It is your determination to represent the class of oppressed people. Whether the ideas are correct or not, it can also be embarrassing to implement. In problem solving, gradual loosening is your method. Conflicts with bosses can occur. Malaria, smallpox, and other epidemics can occur. You are a person who respects the elders. But being more concerned about marriage is in your best interest. Problems in marriage can arise. Problems can be caused by bad women or men. You have to work hard to make money. You are law abiding. But when you make a mistake, you may lose someone in support. Be careful.
</item>
        <item>A pure mind\n
The 5th lucky number belonging to Mercury will bring you a lot of luck. You cannot remain in the same business. Many intellectual pursuits change from time to time. You get self-satisfaction from it. Writing can be similar to your life in art or any other art medium. You can even learn a lot and teach it. It is a weakness to stop what you are starting. Someone who likes diversity. All your work is in order. But unrest in emergencies can disrupt work. Neurological disorders can be caused by weakening of the nerves. Be careful as you may fall prey to scams. Most people will want to associate with you. Your mind is pure.
</item>
        <item>Lives a balanced life\n
The sixth destiny number is subject to the power of Venus. With good manners. You do not make decisions on your own. Respects the opinions of others. He is a person who does not accept anything directly and makes good decisions. The art of working in harmony with anyone is well known. Living a balanced life can make you uncomfortable in a relationship. Someone who associates with anyone in a way that suits them. You who love art have a good marriage. But if the two are not understanding you will be very disappointed. Can earn the respect of society.
</item>
        <item>Above education\n
If the number 7, which shows the power of the cones and the planet Neptune, is yours, you do not want anyone to know your affairs. You are the one who bravely walks towards your goal no matter how many obstacles come. Education can be successful and earn income from it. Looks far-reaching. But the restlessness, the fear, the doubt, the disbelief, make your work mysterious. It can cause skin problems, gastrointestinal diseases, infectious diseases and skin diseases. There is a lot of improvement after adolescence. You look at anything analytically and exploratively. Helping others gets you into trouble.
</item>
        <item>Worldly development\n
Saturn or the 8th house of power will give you a lot of worldly progress. A position that focuses on money management, where leadership is involved. You need to be at work regularly. Frequent travel. He is good at working for himself as well as for others. No matter how much poverty there is, no one is touched. Is someone who protects self-esteem. You can do a lot with experience. Trade, foreign affairs are your heritage. Any grief has the strength to endure trouble. You almost do not need a break. Knee and abdominal pain can be painful.
</item>
        <item>Not afraid of risk\n
Destiny No. 9, which is subject to the power of Mars, will have a strong influence on your marriage. If the spouse does not match, the power of Mars can lead to many conflicts. It is your habit to win the argument about anything. Your story is compelling. It can often be frustrating because it is not accessible to others. You do not want to be frustrated. But you are a brave, proud, fun-loving, militant person who respects justice, sympathizes with those in need. Money can make a difference. Excessive costs need to be controlled. Body temperature, eye problems, headaches, skin diseases are easily caused.
</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="directions">
        <item>උතුරු</item>
        <item>ඊසානදිග</item>
        <item>නැගෙනහිර</item>
        <item>අග්නිදිග</item>
        <item>දකුණු</item>
        <item>නිරිතදිග</item>
        <item>බටහිර</item>
        <item>වයඹ</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>